[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can design your own book covers
你可以设计你自己的书籍封面
using inkscape and i don't just mean a
使用Inkscape，我的意思不仅仅是
book cover for an ebook i mean an actual
电子书的封面，我是说真正的
physical book cover that you would print
您要打印的纸质书籍封面
and use on a book as you can see here in
在一本书上使用，就像你在这里看到的
the mock-up before we get started though
不过，在我们开始之前的模型
if you'd like to learn everything that
如果你想了解所有
there is to know about enscape
有一点是要知道的，那就是
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where i go over
我看过的视频
all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and i explained what they are
Inkscape和我解释了它们是什么
and demonstrate how they work
并演示它们的工作原理
i'll have a link in the description of
我会在描述中有一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
okay so as you can see here i've opened
好的，正如你所看到的，我已经打开了
up the kindle direct publishing
升级Kindle直接发布
uh this is there this is amazon's print
呃，这就是这是亚马逊的指纹
on demand service for uh having your own
按需服务，呃，有你自己的服务
books
书籍
printed i'll be showing you how to use
打印出来的，我会教你如何使用
this service here because this is the
这里的这项服务，因为这是
one that people most commonly use when
人们在以下情况下最常使用的一种
they have books printed
他们的书都印好了
in order to design your book cover with
为了给你的书设计封面
inkscape you first have to come here and
Inkscape你得先来这里
download a template
下载模板
for the size of book you'd like to print
对于您想要打印的书的大小
so if you notice over here we have all
所以如果你注意到这里我们有所有的
these different sizes to choose from we
这些不同的尺码可供我们选择
have a page count to choose from and we
有一个页数可供选择，我们
have
有
color options to choose from for the
可供选择的颜色选项
paper as well for this demonstration
本演示的纸张也是如此
i'll be showing
我会展示给大家
you how to design a six inches by nine
您将如何设计一个六英寸乘九英寸的
inches book with 200 pages in it
英寸厚的书，200页
with white paper now if you go ahead and
现在用白皮书，如果你继续
click the download cover template button
点击下载封面模板按钮
you should get a zip folder and within
您应该得到一个压缩文件夹，并在
that zip folder is a
那个压缩文件夹是一个
dot png file that we will be working
我们将处理的Dot PNG文件
with in inkscape
在Inkscape中使用
okay so getting started here in inkscape
好的，现在开始使用Inkscape
the first thing i want to do is just set
我想做的第一件事就是设定
up the documents that we all have a
把我们所有人都有的文件
similar workflow here
这里有类似的工作流程
i'm going to come up here and turn off
我要到这里来，然后关掉
snapping i want to change the
抓拍我想要更改
units of measurement to pixels and then
像素的测量单位，然后
i will come up here to where it says
我会到上面写着的地方
view and make sure you have custom
查看并确保您有自定义
selected
已选择
and now what i'm going to do is i'm
现在我要做的是
going to import that png template onto
要将该PNG模板导入到
my canvas here by just clicking and
我的画布在这里只需点击和
dragging it onto the canvas like that
像这样把它拖到画布上
now you can't see where this is coming
现在你看不到这是怎么回事了
from because i have this folder opened
因为我打开了此文件夹
up on my other monitor but if you take
在我的另一个监视器上，但如果你拿着
the dot png file
点PNG文件
and click and drag it onto your canvas
点击并将其拖到您的画布上
like that you should get this little
就像这样，你应该得到这个小
this little menu that pops up and from
这个弹出式的小菜单
these defaults here we want to make sure
这里的这些默认设置我们希望确保
we have embed
我们已经嵌入了
from image dpi default import resolution
从图像dpi默认导入分辨率
and for image rendering mode
并用于图像渲染模式
none and once you have those presets as
无，一旦您将这些预置设置为
they are click ok
它们被点击确定
and it should import your image as you
它应该将你的形象导入为你
can see here now let me zoom out a
可以看到这里，现在让我放大一个
little bit so i can see that a little
一点，这样我就能看到一点
better
更好的
you hold ctrl roll down the mouse wheel
按住Ctrl向下滚动鼠标滚轮
a couple of times
有几次
okay so there's our template a couple of
好的，这是我们的几个模板
things about this template
有关此模板的信息
this image right here represents the
这里的这张图片代表
size that our document needs to be so
我们的文档需要这样的大小
what i'm going to do is i want to resize
我要做的是调整大小
the document so that it fits
文档，以使其适合
this image right here now if you notice
如果你注意到这里的这张图片
this is the document size right here as
这里的文档大小如下所示
it stands
它屹立不倒
so in order to change that what i'm
所以为了改变我现在的状态
going to do is i'm going to select the
我要做的就是选择
image
图像
and i'm going to press ctrl shift and r
我要按Ctrl Shift键和r键
on the keyboard
在键盘上
and that's going to change the document
这将改变文件
size to match
要匹配的大小
the size of the selection there as you
所选内容的大小与您的
can see there a couple of more things uh
我能看到更多的东西呢
worth noting about this template over
值得注意的是这个模板
here you'll notice this dotted line
在这里，您会注意到这条虚线
going around the edge
在边缘徘徊
of the image here this dotted line
在这里的图像的这条虚线
represents the bleed cutoff
表示出血截止点
once this document is printed everything
一旦打印了此文档，所有内容
outside of this dotted line will be
在这条虚线之外将是
trimmed off
被修剪掉
and then this pink area right here
然后这个粉色区域就在这里
represents the safe area
表示安全区域
meaning all of your contents of your
意思是您的所有内容
design need to be
设计需要
away from this pink area if you have any
远离这个粉色区域，如果你有
elements like text or imagery that touch
像文本或图像这样的元素
this pink area or start to bleed out
这粉红色的区域或开始出血
into that area
进入那片区域
uh amazon will reject your book cover
呃，亚马逊会拒绝你的书封面
design so that's something important to
设计，所以这是很重要的事情
keep in mind as we're going through and
在我们进行的过程中请记住
creating this design you want to make
创建您想要进行的设计
sure you keep everything
当然，你什么都留着
in this white space in here now as you
在这里的这片白色空间里，现在你
can see over here on the right
在右边可以看到这里
we have the cover of the book the front
我们有这本书的封面在前面
cover over here on the left we have the
掩护在这里在左边我们有
back cover
封底
and this right here is the spine of the
而这就是这根脊梁
book now the way this works is this will
现在登记这项工作的方式是这一意愿
be printed out as one
作为一个整体打印出来
entire document and then just wrapped
整个文档，然后只换行
around the book as a single
围绕着这本书作为一首单曲
a single piece of paper and then over
一张纸，然后就过去了
here we have
我们这里有
the barcode now when we're designing we
现在当我们设计我们的条形码时
want to make sure we do not put anything
想要确保我们不会把任何东西
over here we do not need to put the
在这里，我们不需要将
barcode on the design ourselves amazon
设计上的条形码我们自己亚马逊
will handle that themselves all we have
会自己处理我们所拥有的一切
to do
去做
is make sure that we leave this space
就是确保我们离开这个空间
right here free
就在这里免费
so let me zoom out a little bit let me
所以让我把镜头放大一点，让我
open up the layers menu
打开层菜单
which is located over here you can also
它位于这里，你也可以
press shift control l as a keyboard
按Shift键控制L作为键盘
shortcut
捷径
and what i want to do is i want to
我想做的是我想要
rename this layer to
将此层重命名为
template and i want to create a new
模板和我想创建一个新的
layer
图层
by clicking the plus button over here
通过点击这里的加号按钮
and i want to name this contents
我想把这些内容命名为
all of the contents the design is going
所有要设计的内容
to be on this layer i want to put this
要在这一层上，我想把这个
below current
低于电流
and click add so we have the contents
然后点击Add，这样我们就有了内容
layer where the design is going to be
设计所在的层
and then we have the template layer up
然后我们把模板层放在上面
here which we're going to use for a
在这里，我们将使用它作为
reference as we're creating our design
在我们创建我们的设计时引用
now instead of using this template right
现在不是正确使用这个模板
here i'm just going to create some
在这里，我将创建一些
simple guides to make sure that i'm
简单的指南来确保我是
staying within these boundaries here so
呆在这里的边界内，所以
the first thing i want to do is let me
我想做的第一件事就是让我
grab the rectangles tool
抓取矩形工具
and i'm going to create a rectangle
我要创建一个矩形
going over the white space right here
就在这里的空白区域
of the back cover and i want to give
封底，我想给你
that an outline um
那一个提纲呢
or a stroke i'm going to hold shift and
或者中风，我要按住Shift键
click on the color green to give that
点击绿色即可实现
an outline let me remove the fill color
轮廓允许我删除填充颜色
let me grab the select tool
让我拿一下选择工具
i'm going to be moving through these
我要穿过这些
steps a little quicker than normal this
这一步比平时快了一点
is going to be more of like an
将更像是一种
intermediate tutorial because
中级教程，因为
there's a lot for me to go over in this
在这件事上，我有很多事情要做
lesson so i'm not going to be explaining
这一课，所以我不打算解释
every single click like i normally do so
每一次点击都像我平时那样
that's something to keep in mind
这是一件需要牢记的事情
let me zoom in over here i want to make
让我放大这里，我想要
sure i have this option up here disabled
当然，我在这里禁用了此选项
where it says when scaling objects scale
其中显示在缩放对象时进行缩放
the stroke width by the same
笔触宽度相同
proportion have that turned off and i
这一比例已经关闭，我
just want to make sure
我只想确保
that the edge of this green stroke is
这一绿色笔划的边缘是
resting on the edge
在悬崖边上休息
of this white safe space right here
这个白色的安全空间就在这里
there we go looking pretty good and
我们看起来很不错，而且
again to zoom in and out holding control
再次按住控件进行放大和缩小
rolling up and down the mouse wheel to
上下滚动鼠标滚轮以执行以下操作
move the page around pressing down the
将页面向下移动按下
mouse wheel and moving the mouse
鼠标滚轮和移动鼠标
i want to create another one going over
我想再做一个
this barcode right here
这个条形码就在这里
there we go
好了，我们走吧
i'm going to grab the select tool
我要去拿选择工具
duplicate that by pressing ctrl d
通过按Ctrld复制该命令
i'm going to move this over here like
我要把这个搬到这里来，就像
that
那
and then i'll create another one for the
然后，我将为
spine control d to duplicate it move
脊椎控制%d复制它移动
this one over here
这个就是这里
there we go and i'll just resize that to
好了，我要把它的大小调整到
fit
配合度
the uh i want to make sure it fits the
呃，我想确保它符合
spine right there
脊椎就在那里
okay looking pretty good okay let me
好的，看起来很不错，好的，让我来
just zoom out
只要缩小就行了
okay looking pretty good here we've got
好的，看起来很不错，我们有
uh green strokes for all of the
呃，所有的绿色笔划
important areas
重要领域
what i want to do is i want to select
我想要做的是我想选择
this image the template and i want to
这张图片是我和模板想要的
right click it and go to copy
右键单击它，然后转到复制
and then i want to turn off the
然后我想关掉
visibility of the templates layer i want
我需要的模板图层的可见性
to come down here to the contents layer
来到这里的Contents层
and i want to create another rectangle
我想创建另一个矩形
so just create a rectangle like that
所以只需创建一个这样的矩形
give this a fill color i'm going to make
给这个配上我要做的填充色
this as you can see in the thumbnail
正如您在缩略图中看到的那样
design i made this book cover
设计我做了这本书的封面
yellow with some white going through
黄色和一些白色穿过
here so i'm going to make this yellow
在这里，我要把它变成黄色
the cover out the color i want the book
封面上有我想要的那本书的颜色
cover to be
封面待定
i'll make that yellow let me get rid of
我会把它变成黄色的，让我摆脱它
that stroke by holding shift and
通过按住Shift键和
clicking the x
单击x
and i want to make this the same size as
我想把这件衣服做得和
the template that we just copied so to
我们刚刚复制到的模板
do that
做那件事吧
let me go to edit paste size paste size
让我转到编辑粘贴大小粘贴大小
and it'll paste the width and height of
它会粘贴宽度和高度
that image like that
像这样的形象
and then i just want to align this on
然后我只想把这个对准
the artboard here or the canvas so let
这里的画板或画布让我们
me open up the alignment menu over here
我打开这里的对准菜单
ctrl shift a is the keyboard shortcut
Ctrl Shift a是键盘快捷键
and i'm going to align this relative to
我要将这一相对关系与
the page i'm going to put that on the
这一页我要把它放在
vertical and horizontal axis like that
像这样的垂直轴和水平轴
okay now we'll come back over here to
好的，现在我们回到这里来
the layers menu now that we have that in
Layers菜单现在我们有了它
place
地点
we can select the template layer turn
我们可以选择模板层旋转
the visibility of that back on
它的能见度又回到了
and what i want to do is take this
我想要做的是拿着这个
template and we don't need this anymore
模板，我们不再需要这个
you could just press delete on your
您只需按下Delete键即可
keyboard and get rid of that
键盘，把它扔掉
and as you can see we have the book
如你所见，我们有这本书
cover design which is the yellow
封面设计是黄色的
rectangle
长方形
with these guides in place to let us
有了这些指南，我们就可以
know where the important content should
知道重要内容应该放在哪里
go
去
and where we should not be putting any
以及我们不应该把任何
content so let me
心满意足所以让我
lock this layer so that i don't
锁定此层，这样我就不会
accidentally
无意中
move any of these guides as i'm
移动这些向导中的任何一个，因为我
designing and there we go now i'm going
设计，我们走了，现在我要走了
to click on the contents layer
单击Contents层的步骤
and now we are ready to start designing
现在我们已经准备好开始设计
so as you can see here this book cover
正如你在这里看到的，这本书的封面
is
是
yellow and i have some white in there so
黄色的，我有一些白色的，所以
i'm going to go ahead and create that
我将继续并创建一个
aspect of it real quick let me
快点，让我来看看
take this image right here and duplicate
把这张图片放在这里复制
that by pressing ctrl d
通过按Ctrl d键
and i'm going to make this white and i'm
我要把它变成白色，我要
just going to scale this down like this
就像这样缩小规模
kind of like that now i'm going to grab
就像这样，现在我要抓住
my text tool
我的文本工具
and i'm going to put some text in here
我要在这里输入一些文本
i'm going to write
我要写下
how to create a
如何创建
now let me change the font i'm going to
现在让我更改我要使用的字体
go to text text and font
转到文本文本和字体
and the font i'm looking for is
我要找的字体是
montserrat obviously you can use
蒙特塞拉特显然你可以用
whatever font you'd like i'm just
不管你想要什么字体，我只是
showing you how i created this specific
向你展示我是如何创建这个特定的
design i'm going to apply that font like
设计我将应用该字体，如
that
那
let me scale that up i'm holding ctrl
让我把它放大，我按住Ctrl键
while i scale to lock the proportions
当我缩放以锁定比例时
place this right about there and i'm
把这个放在那里，我就会
going to duplicate that control d
将复制该控件%d
bring that down there and i'm going to
把那个拿下来，我要去
change
变化
this to with inkscape
这与Inkscape有关
and the text in the middle here is going
中间的文字是这样写的
to be a different font let me just make
为了成为一种不同的字体，让我只需将
sure i have this centered up first i'm
当然，我先把这个放好，我是
going to select both of these
我要同时选择这两个选项
come back over here to the align
回到这里来对齐
distribute menu and set this to
“分发”菜单，并将其设置为
last selected and just make sure i have
最后一次选择，只要确保我有
that centered up like that
像这样居中的
now if you notice here i have a book
如果你注意到了，我有一本书
cover design in the middle here with a
封面设计在这里的中间有一个
different font so i'm going to go ahead
不同的字体，所以我要继续
and create that next
并创建下一个
let me grab my text tool again i'm going
让我再拿起我的文本工具，我要走了
to write
写
book cover design
书籍封面设计
there we go let me change the font of
好了，让我更改一下字体
that to
那是为了
sirona make sure i have that
Sirona，确保我拿到了
centered and i'm just going to scale
居中，我只是要扩展
that up as well
那也是一样的
i'm actually going to move this out of
我真的要把这个搬出去
the way i want to make this i want this
我想做这件事我想要这件事
title to take up the whole width of this
标题占据了整个宽度
of this uh of this cover right here just
这本封面的这个，呃，就在这里
like that
就像这样
let me center that up on there
让我把它放在那里的中心
and let me just change this white stripe
让我换一下这条白色条纹
right here to accommodate the change
就在这里，以适应变化
in the size of the text like that let me
在这样的文本大小中，让我
move this up
把这个往上移
move this up now if you notice over here
如果你注意到这里的话，现在把这个移到前面去
i also have these little white stripes
我还有这些白色的小条纹
on the top and bottom of each of them so
在它们的顶部和底部，所以
what i'm going to do is i'm going to
我要做的是我要
duplicate that
复制那个
ctrl d move this over here like this
我会像这样把这个搬到这里来。
and just bring down the height of that
把它的高度降下来
and i'll just duplicate that and bring
我只需要复制一遍，然后带上
that up there
上面的那个
and i want to make sure that all three
我想要确保这三个人
of these white stripes are
这些白色条纹中有
spaced out apart evenly so i'm going to
均匀地分开，所以我要
hold shift and click on each of them
按住Shift键并单击其中的每一个
come over here to align and distribute
请到这里来调整和分发
and click on where it says
并点击它所说的位置
make vertical gaps between objects equal
使对象之间的垂直间距相等
there we go
好了，我们走吧
and now i just want to align my text
现在我只想将我的文本对齐
again to make sure that it's aligned
再次确保其对齐
after that change right there and i'm
在那次改变之后，我就是
just trying to make sure that this is
我只是想确保这是
centered
居中
like that i'm going to take this text
就像这样，我要把这篇文章
and this text
而这篇文章
select them both and then center it up
同时选中它们，然后将其居中
with this text just to make sure that
这篇文章只是为了确保
everything is aligned
一切都对齐了
in the center like that let me move that
在这样的中心，让我移动一下
up
向上
there we go okay so what i'm going to do
好了，现在我要做的是
next
下一首
is down here all of the secrets of book
书中的所有秘密都在这里
cover design revealed
封面设计揭晓
and then by author name let me add that
然后让我用作者的名字来补充一下
text in there real quick
文本在那里真的很快
and i'm going to give this text a little
我要给这篇课文加一点
bit of a shear by clicking on it again
再一次点击它就有点剪切了
and getting these shearing handles just
把这些剪刀把手
to make it look like it's italics
让它看起来像是斜体
because there's no italics version of
因为没有斜体版本的
this font
此字体
let me just do that there we go and i
让我就这么做吧，我们走了，我
want to make sure i have that centered
想确保我把它放在中间吗？
right there
就在那里
there we go and then down here finally i
我们走了，然后下来，最后我
have
有
by author name this is where you put
按作者的名字，这是你放的地方
your author right here so let me
你的作者就在这里，所以让我来
i'm just going to use this text item
我只想用这个文本项
right here i'm going to duplicate that
就在这里，我要重复一遍
by author name and i'll make this one
作者的名字，我会把这个写成
smaller because this one is less
更小，因为这个更小
less prominent there we go put that down
不太显眼的地方，我们要把它放下
there
那里
towards the bottom center that up i want
我想要的是中下角的那个
to make sure i have everything centered
以确保我把所有东西都居中
up here so i'm going to click on
在这里，我要点击
click and drag over all of that make
在所有制造商上单击并拖动
sure it's all centered up like that
当然，都是这样居中的。
and i want to make sure it's all
我想确保这一切都是
centered relative to the page there
相对于页面居中
and what i might want to do is just
我想要做的就是
space things out vertically a little
在垂直方向上把东西分开一点
better so let me move this down
最好还是让我把这个往下移
let me move this down i'm going to group
让我把这个往下移，我要分组了
all of this right here together
所有这一切都在这里
i'm going to just press ctrl g to group
我只需按Ctrl g进入分组
that together like that
就像这样在一起
move this down like this now if you can
如果可以的话现在就像这样把它移下来
see here
看这里
i have the um the inkscape logo up top
我有，呃，Inkscape的标志在上面
there so let me import that in here and
所以让我把它输入到这里，
place that real quick
快点把那个放好
okay so there we go there's the inkscape
好了，我们走吧，这就是墨迹
logo and now i'm just going to select
徽标，现在我要选择
all of these objects or actually you
所有这些对象或者实际上是你
know what let me make sure i have this
知道什么能让我确定我有这个吗
centered first
先居中
there we go i'm going to select all of
好了，我要选择所有
these objects
这些对象
and i just want to space them all apart
我只想把它们分开
evenly vertically like this
像这样均匀地垂直
there we go and maybe move that up a
我们走吧，也许可以把它往上移一步
little bit
一点点
all right we're looking pretty good here
好的，我们现在看起来很不错
okay so what i'm going to do now is the
好的，我现在要做的是
cover of the book
这本书的封面
is now finished i'm going to work on the
现在已经完成了，我要做的是
spine now as you can see in the spine
现在脊椎，就像你在脊椎中看到的
i have the inkscape logo i have the
我有Inkscape徽标，我有
author name i have the title
作者姓名我有这个标题
and then i have some subtext over here
然后我在这里有一些潜台词
so let me add that in here
所以让我在这里补充一下
let me put the escape logo in there i'm
让我把逃生标志放进去，我在
going to duplicate that by pressing ctrl
要通过按Ctrl键复制该命令
d
D
i have to make this small
我得把它弄小一点
there we go put that right about there
好了，我们把它放在那里
and i'm going to put some text right
我要把一些文字改正
here that says the author name
这上面写着作者的名字
let me just duplicate this text and move
让我复制这篇文章，然后移动
it over here
它在这里
and just rotate that around like that so
然后像这样旋转它，这样
that it fits in there
它正好可以放在那里
you may have to scale it down a bit like
你可能不得不把它缩小一点，就像
that there we go
我们走到这一步
now i'm going to put the book title in
现在我要把书名放进去
this white space right here so i'm going
这里的空白处，所以我要
to duplicate
复制
first let me ungroup that i'm going to
首先，让我来解开我要做的
duplicate this design right here i'm
复制这个设计就在这里我在
going to
要去
duplicate this text right here and i
在这里复制此文本，然后我
want to put this text all on one line
我想把这段文字全部放在一行上
like that
就像这样
oops scale that down
哎呀，缩小规模。
rotate that place this in here
把那个地方转到这里
and scale this down so that it doesn't
缩小规模，这样它就不会
it doesn't touch the green edges right
它没有触及正确的绿色边缘
here you want to make sure it's well
在这里，你想要确保它是好的
within that safe area
在那个安全区域内
and then just center that up there we go
然后把它放在中间，我们就开始了
looking pretty good
看起来很不错
now what i'm going to do is i'm going to
现在我要做的是我要
put some subtext down here
在这里写下一些潜台词
uh let me just duplicate this
呃，让我把这个复制一下
the secrets i'm going to i'm going to
我要告诉你的秘密我要告诉你
abbreviate this text so that it doesn't
将这段文字缩写，这样它就不会
take up too much space down here
这里占的空间太大了
the secrets of book cover design let's
书籍封面设计的秘诀让我们来看看
see if that works
看看这招是否管用
okay looking pretty good alright so now
好的，看起来很不错，好的，现在
the spine is finished
脊椎已经完成了
the final step would be to work on the
最后一步将是制定
back cover of the book
这本书的封底
so i'm going to put some text up there
所以我要把一些文字放在上面
some placeholder text in the middle and
中间的一些占位符文本和
then about the author
然后关于作者
uh down there at the bottom so we'll go
呃，在底部，所以我们要走了
ahead and get started on that
走在前面，开始做这件事
i have up here learn how to design book
我在这里学习如何设计书籍
covers okay so i'm going to grab
封面没问题，所以我要去拿
this text i'm going to duplicate that
这篇课文我要复制一下
put this over here i'll make this a
把这个放在这里，我会把它变成一个
little smaller
小一点
let me uh change this learn how to
让我，嗯，改变这一点，学会如何
did i have that on two lines or one line
我是用两行还是一行写的
learn how to
学习如何
design book covers okay learn how to
设计书籍封面好的，学习如何
design book covers
设计书籍封面
perfect i'll scale that down
太好了，我会缩小的。
and now i'm going to put some
现在我要把一些
placeholder text in here some lorem
此处的占位符文本有一些注解
ipsum text you would obviously want to
Ipsum文本您显然想要
write like a description of the book or
像对书的描述那样写，或者
something
某物
this is just a tutorial so i'm going to
这只是一个教程，所以我将
put some lorem if some text in there
如果里面有一些文字，就放一些LOREM
i'll go to extensions render
我将转到扩展渲染
and actually no extensions text and
并且实际上没有扩展文本和
lorem ipsum and i want to choose
Lorem Ipsum和我想选择
two paragraphs six sentences per
两段每句六句
paragraph
段落
and four for the paragraph i'm just
四个是这一段我只是
putting random numbers in here
将随机数放入此处
let me close out of that and this text
让我结束这篇文章和这篇文章
pretty small i got it was generated over
很小的，我得到了它是产生的
here in the top left corner so let me
在左上角，所以让我
let me grab that place this in here let
我来拿一下这里的那个地方，让我
me go to the text editor
我去找文本编辑器
let me select the text with the text
让我选择文本和文本
tool
工具
and i want to change this to montserrat
我想把这个改成蒙特塞拉特
i want to make this uh medium or
我想要这个，呃，中等的或者
semi-bold
半粗体
make this a little bigger maybe 28
把这个做大一点，可能是28
see how that looks maybe a little bigger
看看它看起来怎么样，也许再大一点
than that
比那还多
36. looking better
36.看起来更好了
okay that's good enough i'll leave it at
好的，这就足够了，我就把它留在
36. i'll place this over here towards
36.我把这个放在这边
the top left
左上角
again making sure it's not it's not
再次确认它不是它不是它
going anywhere near that green border
去任何靠近绿色边界的地方
let me go back to the text tool and i'm
让我回到文本工具，然后我
just going to take this little node
我要把这个小节点
right here and bring that
就在这里，把那个拿来
in so that it forces the text within
中，因此它将文本强制放在
this area right here
这片区域就在这里
and then i will center align that text
然后我会将该文本居中对齐
and just to uh let me bring this down a
只是为了，呃，让我把这一点讲下来
little bit
一点点
there we go just to make this look a
我们这样做只是为了让这看起来像是
little better i'm going to add some
好一点，我要加一些
spacing between these lines because
这些行之间的间距，因为
something about this text right here is
关于这里的这篇文章的一些内容是
just not visually appealing it just
只是在视觉上没有吸引力，只是
looks like a cluster of text so
看起来像一串文本，所以
i want to space this out a little bit
我想把这件事隔开一点
let me grab the text tool
让我拿一下文本工具
select that and over here uh spacing
选择那个，然后在这里，呃，间距
between baselines i'm just gonna
在基线之间，我只想
increase that
增加那个
there we go that looks a lot better okay
好了，看起来好多了，好吗？
now down here
现在到下面来
bottom left we have about the author and
左下角我们有关于作者和
some more lorem ipsum
再来点龙舌兰
text so let's go ahead and create that
文本，所以让我们继续创建它
and then we'll be done so let me take
然后我们就完事了，所以让我来
this text let me duplicate that
这篇文章让我重复了这一点
and then i'll just take this text over
然后我会把这篇课文
here and just duplicate that i'll put
在这里复制一份，我会放在
this down here
这就是这里
let me go back to the text tool i'm
让我回到文本工具，我要
going to give this i'm going to align
我要给这个，我要对齐
this to the left
这个在左边
there we go i'll bring this in like this
好了，我要像这样把这个拿进来
and i want to make this text smaller
我想让这篇文章变得更小
this is less prominent if you're
这一点不那么突出，如果你
following
以下是
the rules of visual hierarchy here this
视觉层次的规则在这里
here is the most prominent this is
这是最突出的，这是
secondary and then this is
第二，然后这是
uh down here the least important text
呃，在这里，最不重要的文本
let me uh
让我来吧
shrink that down let me try 24.
把它缩小点，让我试试24号。
see how that looks okay that looks
看看它看起来怎么样，看起来很好
pretty good
挺不错的
i'm gonna get rid of some of these lines
我要去掉这些台词中的一些
of text in here so that it's not
在这里的文本，所以它不是
bleeding out into the uh the bleed cut
出血流进了呃流血的伤口
off
关闭
um there we go
嗯，我们走吧
and if you want you could add like a
如果你愿意，你可以添加一个
little picture right here a picture of
小照片就在这里，一张照片
the author and
作者和
you know whatever else you want to add
你知道你还有什么要补充的
in there okay so the design portion of
在那里，好的，所以设计部分
the book cover is finished
这本书的封面已经完成了
okay so how do we go from here to having
好的，那么我们如何从这里到有
an actual file that we can send to the
我们可以将实际文件发送到
printers and have printed
打印机和已打印的
what we want to do first is come over
我们首先要做的就是过来
here to the layers menu and where it
此处到层菜单以及它所在的位置
says template we want to just turn off
说模板我们只想关闭
the visibility of that layer we don't
这一层的可见性我们不知道
need that anymore
再也不需要它了
and what we want to do now is export
我们现在要做的是出口
this as a jpeg image so we'll go to file
这是一张jpeg图像，所以我们将转到文件中
and we'll go to export png image it's
然后我们要去导出PNG图像
labeled as png image but it also allows
标记为PNG图像，但它也允许
you to export other formats such as jpg
您可以导出其他格式，如jpg
if you're working with inkscape version
如果您正在使用Inkscape版本
1.1 or later so let's open up the export
1.1或更高版本，因此让我们打开出口
menu
菜单
and i want to leave all of the defaults
我想保留所有默认设置
as they are the export area we are
因为他们是我们的出口地区
exporting the page
正在导出页面
and just leave all of these defaults as
只需将所有这些缺省值保留为
they are and then just go ahead and
他们是，然后继续往前走
click on export as and when you click on
当您点击时，点击导出
that it's gonna it's gonna ask you to
它会它会要求你
choose a location on your hard drive to
在您的硬盘上选择一个位置
save this file to
将此文件保存到
and it's also going to ask you to it's
它也会邀请你去它的
also going to ask you to choose a file
我还将要求您选择一个文件
format
格式
now for this probably a good idea to
现在，这可能是一个好主意
choose jpeg
选择jpeg
so um yeah whenever you're printing
所以，嗯，是的，当你打印的时候
something jpeg is always better than png
Jpeg格式的总是比png格式的好。
and once you save that file you should
一旦保存了该文件，您就应该
be done you should be able to take that
做完了，你应该可以拿着它
file that jpeg file that you've exported
文件您已经导出的jpeg文件
and upload it to kindle direct
并将其上传到Kindle Direct
publishing
出版
to have your book cover printed so i
把你的书封面印出来，这样我
think that should do it for this
我觉得这样就够了
tutorial that's how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
designing your own book covers
设计你自己的书籍封面
using inkscape if you have any questions
如果您有任何问题，请使用Inkscape
just leave a comment below and as always
只需在下面留下评论，一如既往
thanks for watching
感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]